President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Records of the Office of the President, 1948-1977; 10; 50 cubic ft.
  - Athletics Policy and Council, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center Responsibilities, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center Responsibilities, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center Responsibilities, 1968-1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center Responsibilities, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Audit Report - SUNY Financial and Operating Practices, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Benevolent Association, 1965-1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Birth Control Program, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Black Faculty, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Budget Monthly Expenditures Report, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Budget Monthly Expenditures Report, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Budget Monthly Expenditures Report, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Budget Monthly Expenditures Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Budget Message, President's, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Draft Counseling Committee, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Drug Education Program, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Dudley Observatory, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dudley Observatory, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dudley Observatory, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Dudley Observatory, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - E-Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ebenezer Howard, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Economic Education, 1965-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Edison Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Educational Communications Center, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Educational Communications Center, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Educational Communications Center, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Educational Communications, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Educational Flexibility Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Educational Opportunity Center, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Educational Opportunities Program, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Educational Opportunities Program, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Educational Opportunities, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Educational Opportunities Program, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - EOP Advisory Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - EOP Director Search, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - EOP Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - EOP Student Association, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Energy Conservation, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Entertainment Expenses, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Environmental Decision Commission Minutes of Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Environmental Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Program, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - EEOP Program, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - EEO Advisory Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - EEOP, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - EEO Workshop Mohawk Campus, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Experimental College, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - External Degree, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Organization for Academic Responsibility, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Complaints, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Complaints, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Conference on the Scientific Revolution, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Congress of the United States, 1969-1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Corning, Erastus, 1966-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Convocation, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Crisis Committee, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - CSEA, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - CSEA, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Cypress Institute, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Care Center, Day, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Day Files - Feb. 1972, 1972 February (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Day Files - March 1972, 1972 March (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Day Files - April 1972, 1972 April (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Day Files - May 1972, 1972 May (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Day Files - June 1972, 1972 June (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Day Files - July 1972, 1972 July (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Day Files - August 1972, 1972 August (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Day Files - September 1972, 1972 September (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Day Files - October 1972, 1972 October (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Day Files - November 1972, 1972 November (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Day Files - December 1972, 1972 December (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Day Files-January 1973, 1973 January (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Day Files - Feb. 1973, 1973 February (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Day Files - March 1973, 1973 March (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Day Files - April 1973, 1973 April (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Day Files - May 1973, 1973 May (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Day Files - June 1973, 1973 June (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Day Files - July 1973, 1973 July (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Day Files - August 1973, 1973 August (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Day Files - September 1973, 1973 September (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Day Files - October 1973, 1973 October (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Day Files - November 1973, 1973 November (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Day Files - December 1973, 1973 December (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Decentralization, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - DA's Readiness Team, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Doctor of Arts Program, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Doctor of Arts Program, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Development Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Development: McLean Associates "A Study of Attitudes and Funding Potentialities", 1972 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Downtown Campus, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Downtown Medical Center - Report of the President( Joseph K. Hill), 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - President: Annual Report, Undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - "F" Miscellaneous, 1968-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Faculty, 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Faculty By-laws, 1965-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Emeriti, 1966-1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Information Hours, 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Faculty: Status of Women, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1956-1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Workload, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fellowships, Grants, 1967-1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Financial Aids Office, 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - FM Radio Station, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - FSA Bookstore, 1965-1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - FSA-Budgets/Financial Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - FSA-Budgets/Financial Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - FSA By-Laws, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - FSA Financial Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - FSA Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - FSA Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - FSA Salaries and Personnel Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Full Opportunity Program, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - "G" Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General Electric, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - General Electric, 1966-1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Gerontology Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Gift to College, 1934-1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Governance Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Office, 1965-1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Task Force Campus Ad-Hoc Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Task Force, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Task Force - Correspondence, Press Releases, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Task Force - Personnel, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Task Force Working Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Task Force, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Grading System(S-U), 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Studies, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Studies, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Studies, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Studies, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "H" Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Health Services, 1967-1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Hillel, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Homecoming, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Housing, 1966-1973 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Hudson-Mohawk Association., 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Humanistic Education, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - "I" Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Inauguration, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Innovative Education, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Institute of International Education, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Institute on Man & Science, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Institutional Research, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Institutional Research, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Institutional Research, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Interdepartmental Biochemistry Program, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Interdisciplinary Major, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - International Students, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - International Students, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - International Students, 1965-1970 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - International Programs, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - International Programs, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Invitations, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - International Programs, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - International Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "J" Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Joint Committee on Procedures, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Journalism Education, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Judicial Process, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Justice Department, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "K" Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kuntsler Appearance, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "L" Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Labor Management Committee, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Law Suits, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Lecture Series, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Legislature - New York State, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Legislature - New York State, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Library, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Library, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Legislature - New York State, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Library, 1966-1970 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Local Foundations Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Local Foundations Committee, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - "M" Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Master Plan, SUNY, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Master Plan, SUNY, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - May,1970 Crisis(Student Strike, Vietnam War), Undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Medical Technology, 1965-1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Middle States Association, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - "N" Miscellaneous, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - NASULGC, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - NASULGC, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - NASULGC, 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - National Council for Accreditation for Teacher Education, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - NCA/FRACHE, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - NCA/FRACHE, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Nepotism, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Non-Teaching Professionals, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Northeastern New York Speech Center, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Accelerator Lab., 1972 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Accelerator Lab., 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "O" Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Organization Charts, 1958-1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Outstanding Teacher Award Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "P" Miscellaneous, 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Penal Reform Committee, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Penal Reform Committee, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Penal Reform Committee, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - PERB, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Parking, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Parking, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Parking, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Peace Institute, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Performance Rating Board, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Performance Arts Center, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Perlmutter, O.W., 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Personnel, 1968-1973 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Kuusisto Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Physical Plant, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Physical Plant, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Physical Plant, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Physical and Development General, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Placement Office, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Placement Office (Next 10 Folders), Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Accelerator Building, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dormitories, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - East and West Podium Courts, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fuller Brush Company, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Indian Quad Conversion, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Married Student Housing, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Motor Vehicle Housing, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Physical Education Building II(Field House), Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Pine Bush Sewer, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Planning Task Force/Enrollment, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Planning Task Force/Enrollment, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Planning Task Force/Enrollment, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Planning Task Force/Enrollment, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Pre-Registration Proposal, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Princeton Report(Middle States Association), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Princeton Evaluation(MSA), 1972 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Princeton Evaluation(MSA), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Princeton Evaluation(Documents), 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Professional Evaluation Committee, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Project Themis, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Protest DOW Chemical, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Publications, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - "R" Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "R" Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Reclassifications, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Registrar, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Registrar, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Regional Hospital Review and Planning Council, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Reintsema, Joris, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Religious Holy Days, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Reorganization, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Research and Graduate Studies, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Office of Research Monthly Report, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Office of Research Monthly Reports, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Research Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Research Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Research Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Research Funds and Awards, 1966-1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Research Park, Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Trust, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Robles, Mireya, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Round Table Luncheons, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - "S" Miscellaneous, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Scholarships, Awards, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Sea Grant Governing Board, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Sea Grant Governing Board, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Senate Professional Association, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Senate Professional Association, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Senate Professional Association, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Sigma Xi, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Smith Fund, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Space Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Space Needs, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Space Needs, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Space Needs, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - State Education Department, 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - State Education Department, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - State Education Department, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - State University Professional Association, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Strike Policy, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Student Activates, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Student Activity Fees, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Student Association, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Student Association, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Student Conferences, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Student Association of State University of New York (SASU), 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Summer Sessions, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Summer Sessions, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - SUNYA Field Audit, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - "T" Miscellaneous, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Tuition, Fees, and Charges, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Two-Year College-Student Development Center, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - "U" Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1965-1970 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - University Awards, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - United Fund, 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - University Breakfast, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - University Center Concept, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - University Center Concept, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - University College, 1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - University Communications, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - University Council, 1960-1973 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - University Senate, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - University Senate, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - University Senate, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Urban Fellowship Program, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - "V" Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Vice President for Management and Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Vice President for Management and Planning, 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Vice President for Research, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Vice President for University Affairs, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Vice President for University Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Wage-Price Freeze, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Weston, M. Moran, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "W" Miscellaneous, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - West Podium Extension, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - East Podium Extension, 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Wagner Case, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Wagner Case, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Wheelock Scholarship, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Women's Lib, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Women's Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - WSUA-Radio, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - X-Y-Z Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - School of Criminal Justice, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - School of Criminal Justice, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - School of Criminal Justice, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - School of Criminal Justice Development Plan, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - School of Criminal Justice Report on Campus Disorder, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Criminal Justice Visiting Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - School of Criminal Justice Visiting Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - School of Criminal Justice Visiting Committee, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Pinkerton Foundation, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - School of Education, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - School of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - School of Education, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Business Education, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Counseling & Personnel Services, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Curriculum, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Educational Administration, 1965-1969 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Educational Communication, 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Educational Psychology & Statistics, 1964-1973 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1968-1973 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - American Association of University Women, 1964-1973 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - SUNY Chancellor, 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Admissions Processing Center, 1962-1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Architecture and Facilities, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Area Studies, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - SUNY College & University Correspondence, 1958-1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - University Construction Fund, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Council of Presidents, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Council of Presidents, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Council of Presidents, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - SUNYA Councils Office, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - SUNY-Committees, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - SUNY-Empire State College, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - SUNY Personnel and Employee Relations, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - SUNY Personnel and Employee Relations, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - SUNY Open Access, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - SUNY International Education, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - SUNY Provost, 1964-1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - SUNY University Center - Buffalo, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor, 1966-1971 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Administration, 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Business Affairs, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Conference of Presidents, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Education Communication, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for Finance & Management, 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University Affairs, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University Centers & Contract Colleges, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University Wide Activities, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Washington Office, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - SUNY Vice Chancellor for University Wide Activates, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Rensselaerville Institute, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - SUNY - University Center Presidents, 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Bower, Warren, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Applications - Recommendations, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Applications - Recommendations (E-I), 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Applications - Recommendations (E-I), 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Applications - Recommendations (J-M), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Applications - Recommendations (J-M), 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Applications - Recommendations (N-R), 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Applications - Recommendations (N-R), 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Applications - Recommendations, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Applications - Recommendations (S-Z), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Applications - Recommendations (S-Z), 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - University Senate Bills, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - University Senate Bills, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)